Contact

kathrynaudery@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kathryn-audery-32a4b57a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Acute Care

BLS

Critical Care

Certifications

Certified Nurse Operative Room (CNOR)

Kathryn Audery

BSN,RN,CNOR

League City, Texas

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Surgical services, Patient Advocacy, Nursing Education and Medical-Surgical. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing and CNOR certified.

Experience

The University of Texas Medical Branch Operating Room Nurse October 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months) League City, Texas

Mainland Medical Ctr

3 years 4 months

Operating Room Nurse

October 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Texas City, Texas

Medical Surgical Nurse

July 2013 - October 2015 (2 years 4 months)

Texas City, Texas

Education

WGU Texas

Bachelor's of Science Nursing, Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

Galveston College

Associates Degree of Nursing, Registered nurse (2011 - 2014)